wsecu.org 2019-09-18

# FACTS WHAT DOES WASHINGTON STATE EMPLOYEES CREDIT UNION (WSECU) ANDWSECU SERVICE COMPANY, LLC, QCASH FINANCIAL, LLC AND ONE WASHINGTON FINANCIAL, LLC DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION? Why?

REVISED 01/2016                                                                                                                MKT-852 01.16
                           WHAT DOES WASHINGTON STATE EMPLOYEES CREDIT UNION (WSECU) AND
         FACTS             WSECU SERVICE COMPANY, LLC, QCASH FINANCIAL, LLC AND ONE WASHINGTON
                           FINANCIAL, LLC DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
                           Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the
         Why?              right to limit some — but not all — sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share,
                           and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
                           The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us.
                           This information can include:
         What?             • Social Security Number            • Credit history
                           • Account balances                  • Income
                           • Transaction history               • Credit scores
                           All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business.
         How?              In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal
                           information; the reasons WSECU chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
   Reasons we can share your personal information                    Does WSECU share?                   Can you limit this sharing?
    For our everyday business purposes —
    such as to process your transactions, maintain
    your account(s), respond to court orders and legal                         Yes                                   No
    investigations, or report to credit bureaus
    For our marketing purposes —
    to offer our products and services to you                                  Yes                                   Yes
    For joint marketing with other financial companies                         Yes                                   Yes
    For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes —
    information about your transactions and experiences                        Yes                                   No
    For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes —
    information about your creditworthiness                                    No                               We don’t share
    For our affiliates to market to you                                        Yes                                   Yes
    For non-affiliates to market to you                                        No                               We don’t share
                           • Call 800.562.0999
                           • Visit us online at wsecu.org and click on Terms & Conditions
        To limit           Please note:
           our             • If you are a new member, we can begin sharing your information with our affiliates so they can market
        sharing               to you 30 days from the date we send this notice.
                           • When you are no longer a member, we will continue to share your information as described in this notice.
                           • You can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
      Questions?           Call toll-free 800.562.0999 or go to wsecu.org.
                                                                                                                                  Page 1 of 2

REVISED 01/2016
   Who We Are
                                  Washington State Employees Credit Union (WSECU) and WSECU Service Company, LLC,
   Who is providing this notice?
                                  QCash Financial, LLC and One Washington Financial, LLC.
   What We Do
                                  To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security
                                  measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and
   How does WSECU protect
                                  secured files and buildings.
   my personal information?
                                  We also maintain other physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect this information
                                  and we limit access to information to those employees for whom access is appropriate.
                                  We collect your personal information, for example, when you:
                                  • Open an account                          • Use your credit or debit card
   How does WSECU collect
   my personal information?       • Pay your bills                           • Make deposits or withdrawals from your account
                                  • Apply for a loan
                                  We also collect your personal information from credit bureaus and other companies.
                                  Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
                                  • Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes — information about your creditworthiness
   Why can’t I limit all sharing? • Affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                  • Sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
                                  State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
   What happens when I limit
   sharing for an account I hold  Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
   jointly with someone else?
   Definitions
                                  Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                                  non-financial companies.
                                  Our affiliates include:
   Affiliates
                                  • WSECU Service Company, LLC
                                  • QCash Financial, LLC, a provider of financial services, including cash management
                                  • One Washington Financial (OWF), a provider of financial services, including mortgages.
                                  Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
   Non-affiliates                 non-financial companies.
                                  • WSECU does not share with non-affiliates so they can market to you.
                                  A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market
   Joint marketing                financial products or services to you.
                                  • Our joint marketing partners include providers of investment and financial services and
                                     insurance companies.
                                                                                                                              Page 2 of 2
